Before you start with your spray tan, you want to make sure that your area is completely covered or protected.
If you're doing this at home, maybe do it in the shower or even outside for that matter, in the middle of a large area, maybe not, definitely not on a carpeted area or anywhere where there's fabric.
Maybe lay plastic or old towel.
Here we have everything covered with plastic so it's totally protected and whatever is not covered can be mopped, cleaned, it comes clean, it's just a matter of cleaning.
I always wear gloves when I'm doing, when you're the one doing the spray tan.
If you're spraying yourself, maybe wear gloves until the last minute.
Make sure you have Kleenex nearby because if there's any drips, you want to make sure you get those up immediately.
Make sure your area is pay close attention to make sure that anything that is absorbent, fabrics are your biggest thing that the spray would absorb to.
Your can sprays that you buy in a store also have the same DHA active ingredient but it's not the strength, like a prescription strength like what we use here.
So it probably will come out of your fabrics a little easier but again, make sure you're spraying in an area that is nonporous, would be the best way to put that.